<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Focus On on 黑暗民谣</title>
    <link>http://maintiendrai.github.io/categories/focus-on/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Focus On on 黑暗民谣</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 12:09:09 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://maintiendrai.github.io/categories/focus-on/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Remedies for Sinus Headache Cure</title>
      <link>http://maintiendrai.github.io/post/2014-04-22-sinus-headache-cure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 12:09:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maintiendrai.github.io/post/2014-04-22-sinus-headache-cure/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;被蝶窦炎困扰11年了，蝶窦炎导致头痛真是让人。网上找了篇文章，貌似还挺靠谱的。分享给与我一样受到鼻窦炎困扰的朋友，文章的题目是：治疗窦性头痛的家庭秘方&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.buzzle.com/articles/sinus-headache-home-remedies.html&#34;&gt;http://www.buzzle.com/articles/sinus-headache-home-remedies.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;warm-water&#34;&gt;Warm Water&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The simplest of home remedies is to drink a lot of warm water. I will suggest, whenever you drink water, drink only warm water. If possible, you can drink hot water as well. It will help in minimizing the symptoms sooner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;温水&#34;&gt;温水&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;最简单的偏方是喝大量的热水。 我建议,每当你喝水,只喝温水。 如果可能的话,你可以喝热水。 这将有助于减少症状。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;vitamin-c&#34;&gt;Vitamin C&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In case of a common cold or sinusitis, doctors always advice to increase the consumption of food rich in Vitamin C. Vitamin C is rich in antioxidants, which help fight sinus infection itself and boost the immune system of the body. Vitamin C rich food include strawberries, gooseberry, cauliflower, broccoli, pineapples, oranges, lemon and pomegranates. All these foods are easy to procure and easy to include in your diet. If you are a tea drinker, then you can try lemon tea or lemon green tea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;维生素c&#34;&gt;维生素C&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;对于普通感冒或鼻窦炎,医生总是建议食用富含维生素C的食物。维生素C富含抗氧化剂,帮助对抗窦感染自己,提高身体的免疫系统。 维生素C丰富的食物包括草莓、醋栗、菜花、西兰花、菠萝、橙子、柠檬和石榴。 所有的这些食物都容易在你的饮食中获取。 如果你喜欢喝茶,那么你可以试试柠檬茶或柠檬绿茶。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;hot-and-cold-compress&#34;&gt;Hot and Cold Compress&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alternate hot and cold compresses on the sinus areas help in relieving blocked sinuses. Warm compress should be placed for three minutes and cold compress should be placed immediately for 30 seconds. This alternate compress remedy should be repeated 3 to 5 times in a day for fast relief from blocked sinuses and headache.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;热的和冷的压缩&#34;&gt;热的和冷的压缩&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;热敷和冷敷交替有助于缓解阻塞鼻窦窦区域。 温敷应放置三分钟和冷敷应立即放置30秒。 这个替代补救措施应该在一天内重复3 - 5次的快速缓解阻塞鼻窦和头痛。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;house-ventilation&#34;&gt;House Ventilation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To keep the house warm, we often tend to seal up the house, although this makes the house energy-efficient, it also leads to the house becoming a breeding ground for different microbes, which often leads to aggravating the condition. Therefore, it is important that you ventilate your house well all the time and let some fresh air into the house often.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;房子通风&#34;&gt;房子通风&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;保持房子温暖,我们常常倾向于密封的房子,尽管这使得房子更节能,但它导致了房子成为不同微生物的滋生,这常常会加重病情。 因此,重要的是,你的房子要通风好,经常让一些新鲜空气进屋里。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;humidify-the-nasal-passages&#34;&gt;Humidify the Nasal Passages&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a misconception, that dry air is better to heal sinus infection. However, it is far from truth, as it is actually the humid air, which helps in healing the condition faster. When the air is dry it irritates the nasal passages and they are then inflamed. You can either use a humidifier or a vaporizer. If you do not have any one of them, then you can take long hot showers a couple of times a day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;使鼻腔湿润&#34;&gt;使鼻腔湿润&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;有一种误解,干燥的空气更好治疗鼻窦感染。 然而,这个远离真理,因为它实际上是潮湿的空气,这有助于在它的治愈。 当空气干燥时它会刺激鼻腔和发炎。 您可以使用加湿器或汽化器。 如果你没有任何其中之一,那么你可以花很长时间每天热水淋浴几次。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;warm-soups&#34;&gt;Warm Soups&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make warm soups a part of your diet. Warm soup will help you to get rid of nasal congestion. You can add a generous amount of pepper to your soup. If you like it, you can try adding pepper to your tea as well. Drink your tea as warm as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;温暖的汤&#34;&gt;温暖的汤&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;让温暖的汤你的饮食的一部分。 温暖的汤会帮助你摆脱鼻塞。 您可以添加一个慷慨的辣椒汤。 如果你喜欢它,你也可以尝试在你的茶里添加辣椒。 喝你的茶保证尽可能的温暖。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;spicy-food&#34;&gt;Spicy Food&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since you have sinus, food probably does not taste, the best. Therefore, you can try a spicy Mexican or Thai meal. The spicy meal will help in clearing out nasal blockages. Once the blockages are cleared your headache will also be cured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;辣的食物&#34;&gt;辣的食物&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;因为你的鼻窦炎,食品可能没有味道,最好的。 因此,你可以试着辛辣的泰国或墨西哥餐。 辣粉将帮助清理鼻腔阻塞。 一旦堵塞清理你的头痛也将被治愈。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;well-balanced-diet&#34;&gt;Well-Balanced Diet&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although one does not feel like eating, when one is suffering from cold and headache, it is important that one has a well-balanced diet. Having a well-balanced diet ensures the body&amp;rsquo;s immunity is at its best and the body is able to fight the infection better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;均衡的饮食&#34;&gt;均衡的饮食&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;虽然当一个人患有感冒和头痛会不太想进食,但是一个有一个均衡的饮食是很重要的。 有一个均衡的饮食可以确保身体的免疫力是最好的,身体能够更好的抵御感染。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;ginger&#34;&gt;Ginger&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ginger helps in sinus headache relief, as it has anti-inflammatory properties. The medicinal properties of ginger also include pain relief and relief from headaches. You can add ginger to your tea as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;姜&#34;&gt;姜&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;姜有助于窦头痛缓解,因为它有消炎的作用。 姜的药用价值也包括止痛和缓解头痛。 你可以添加姜茶。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;steam&#34;&gt;Steam&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can boil water in a saucepan and inhale the steam. If you are not allergic to eucalyptus and it is readily available at home, add a couple of drops of eucalyptus oil to your steamed water. The other way of using eucalyptus oil, is to dab some on your forehead. Be careful as the vapors are strong. If you are trying it for the first time, then do not be generous with the quantity of eucalyptus oil. Peppermint oil can also be added to the steam water for quick relief. Like eucalyptus oil, peppermint oil will also help to relieve nasal congestion and calm the mucous membrane. The other option is to mix apple cider vinegar and water together. Use this mixture for your steam inhalation. This will help you to get rid of your headache.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;你可以在一个平底锅煮水,吸入蒸汽。 如果你对桉树不过敏,是现成的在家里,添加几滴桉树油蒸水。 使用其他方式把桉树油涂一些在你的额头。 小心蒸汽强劲。 如果你是第一次尝试,然后不要食用太多桉树油。 薄荷油也可以被添加到蒸汽水快速救援。 如桉树油,薄荷油也将有助于缓解鼻塞,平静的粘膜。 另一种选择是苹果醋和水混合在一起。 使用这种混合蒸汽吸入。 这将帮助你摆脱你的头疼。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;saline-spray&#34;&gt;Saline Spray&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the nasal passages are congested and you are finding it difficult to breathe, then you can make use of a nasal saline spray, to get rid of nasal congestion. Make a spray using warm water and salt and spray it into both the nostrils. It will help in moistening the nasal cavity and relieve congestion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;盐水喷雾&#34;&gt;盐水喷雾&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果鼻腔充血,你发现很难呼吸,然后你就可以利用鼻盐水喷雾,摆脱鼻塞。 做一个喷雾使用温水和盐从两个鼻孔喷进去。 它将帮助滋润鼻腔,缓解交通拥堵。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;neti-pot&#34;&gt;Neti Pot&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using Neti pot will help in clearing the sinuses, which in turn will help to reduce headache. Combine a teaspoon of salt with half teaspoon of baking soda with 1 pint of lukewarm water. Pour the water solution in the Neti pot. Now take the Neti pot in your hand, tilt your head, so that it is at a 45 degree angle. The opening of the Neti pot should be placed on the opening of the top nostril. Now gently pour the contents into the nostril cavity and slowly it will make its way out of the other nostril. Once the saline water is over, blow both the nostril, so any remaining bits of saline water comes out of it. Repeat the same procedure on the other nostril as well. At the end, blow both the nostrils, so that mucus also comes out and the nasal passage is clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;洗鼻壶&#34;&gt;洗鼻壶&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;使用洗鼻壶将有助于清除鼻窦,这反过来将有助于减少头痛。 把一茶匙盐和半茶匙小苏打1品脱温水。 洗鼻壶把水倒的解决方案。现在洗鼻壶在你的手,倾斜你的头,在45度角。 的洗鼻壶应该放置在开放的鼻孔。 现在轻轻地把内容倒进鼻孔腔,慢慢地会使摆脱另一个鼻孔。 一旦咸水,吹两鼻孔,所以任何剩余的盐水出来。 另鼻孔重复相同的过程。 最后,吹两个鼻孔,粘液也出来和鼻腔通道是明确的。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;jalapeno-peppers&#34;&gt;Jalapeno Peppers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this sinus headache home remedy is a little jarring, but it will help you nevertheless in draining the sinuses. Once your sinus is drained, it will be provide instant sinus headache relief. Jalapeño pepper is the answer. Eating a jalapeño pepper drains sinuses within minutes of eating and provides relief from headaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;墨西哥胡椒&#34;&gt;墨西哥胡椒&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;我知道这窦性头痛的家庭治疗方法是有点刺耳,但它将帮助你在鼻窦排水。 一旦你的窦消耗殆尽,它将提供即时窦头痛缓解。 答案是墨西哥辣椒。 墨西哥胡椒吃下水道鼻窦吃后几分钟内,并提供缓解头痛。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;cinnamon&#34;&gt;Cinnamon&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon is a herb which helps a great deal in a sinus headache cure. Mix one tablespoon of powdered cinnamon with water and apply the paste on your forehead for quick relief from your sinus headache. So that the skin does not burn add half teaspoon of sandalwood powder to the mixture, before applying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;肉桂&#34;&gt;肉桂&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;肉桂是草这有助于在窦性头痛的治疗。 将一汤匙肉桂粉和水混合,额头上的粘贴申请快速缓解你的窦性头痛。 这样皮肤不烧加半茶匙檀香木粉混合物,在应用之前。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;hot-footbath&#34;&gt;Hot Footbath&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next sinus headache home remedy can sound a little funny. Nevertheless it brings sinus headache relief. A hot footbath with a cold compress on the forehead, will relieve you of your painful sinus headache.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;热洗脚&#34;&gt;热洗脚&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;下一次窦头痛补救可以听起来有点好笑。 然而它将窦头痛缓解。 热洗脚冷压缩的额头,窦性头痛会减轻你的痛苦。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;irritants&#34;&gt;Irritants&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We knowingly or unknowingly come in contact with a number of irritants, like cigarette smoke, hairspray, different cleaning products, room fresheners, etc. The fumes from this product cause the condition to flare up. Therefore, it is recommended that one stays away from these irritants as far as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;刺激物&#34;&gt;刺激物&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;我们有意或无意接触刺激物,像香烟,发胶,不同的清洁产品,房间清新剂等。烟雾从这个产品导致状态爆发。 因此,建议尽量远离这些刺激物。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;pressure-point&#34;&gt;Pressure Point&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last but not the least, you can use sinus pressure relief techniques, to rid yourself of the nagging headache. One such technique to relieve sinus pressure is to apply pressure on the point where the thumb and index finger of your hands meet. Apply as much pressure as possible. This will bring instant relief from your headache.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;压力点&#34;&gt;压力点&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;最后但也是很重要的,您可以使用窦减压技术,摆脱自己的唠叨头痛。 这样一个技术来缓解鼻窦压力施压的双手的拇指和食指。 申请尽可能多的压力。 这将带来即时减轻你的头疼。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have also heard about sinus wash as one of the sinus headache remedies, but it is best done under medical supervision. I will however suggest you speak with your health care provider before you use any of these sinus headache home remedies. Do you want to know what works the best with me in case of a sinus headache? It is good sleep. Nothing can be as soothing as a good sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;我还听说窦洗的窦性头痛的治疗方法,但最好是在医疗监督下完成的。 然而我将建议你之前和你的卫生保健提供者使用这些窦头痛的补救措施。 你想知道什么工作最好的对于窦头痛吗? 这是良好的睡眠。 没有什么可以舒缓的作为一个良好的睡眠。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>